export default data = [
  {
      question: "Jack is a ______ person: he is polite, kind, and always shows respect for others",
      options: ["courteous","handsome","hateful","sensitive"],
      correct_option: "courteous"
  },
  {
      question: "The traffic in the city was ______ today, so Jane got home earlier than usual",
      options: ["heavy","weak","scarce","light"],
      correct_option: "light"
  },
  {
      question: "Jonathan had qualified as a doctor but later gave up the ______ of medicine for full-time writing",
      options: ["treatment","diagnosis","practice","consumption"],
      correct_option: "practice"
  },
  {
      question: "Bill was severely punished because he ______ lied to his mother",
      options: ["notoriously","purposefully","roughly","strongly"],
      correct_option: "purposefully"
  },
  {
      question: "The two security guards will be ______ from all their duties until further investigation is completed",
      options: ["collapsed","measured","declared","suspended"],
      correct_option: "suspended"
  },
  {
      question: "He made his instruction ______ and direct so that everyone could follow easily",
      options: ["tentative","explicit","plausible","informal"],
      correct_option: "explicit"
  },
  {
      question: "In order for a new product to sell well, manufacturers often invest a large sum of money on its ______",
      options: ["liberation","promotion","destruction","concentration"],
      correct_option: "promotion"
  },
  {
      question: "The soldier was put on trial for ______ to obey his commanding officer’s order",
      options: ["refusing","regretting","resigning","restricting"],
      correct_option: "refusing"
  },
  {
      question: "Since Michael was the best candidate, the committee voted ______ for him to take charge of the company’s sales department",
      options: ["anonymously","drastically","customarily","unanimously"],
      correct_option: "unanimously"
  },
  {
      question: "After hiking all day without drinking any water, the students sat down by the stream to quench their ______",
      options: ["hunger","energy","thirst","nutrition"],
      correct_option: "thirst"
  },
  {
      question: "The more one is ______ the English-speaking environment, the better he or she will learn the language",
      options: ["filled in","exposed to","caught on","kept up"],
      correct_option: "exposed to"
  },
  {
      question: "Peter’s sudden death was a great blow to Jane and it took her a long time to ______ the grief",
      options: ["put out","come across","go round","get over"],
      correct_option: "get over"
  },
  {
      question: "A person who likes to ______ others is definitely not easy to get along with",
      options: ["leave out","let off","pick on","turn up"],
      correct_option: "pick on"
  },
  {
      question: "The old houses will soon be ______ and rebuilt because of the severe damage caused by the earthquake",
      options: ["put out","run down","knocked out","pulled down"],
      correct_option: "pulled down"
  },
  {
      question: "I’d like to thank you for your hospitality ______ our group",
      options: ["on behalf of","instead of","because of","as a result of"],
      correct_option: "on behalf of"
  },
]
